const questions = [
    {
        question: `"The Matrix": "I know why you're here; Neo. I know what you've been doing... why you hardly sleep; why you live alone and why; night after night; you sit by your computer." Who said this to Neo?`,
        answer: 'Trinity',
        explanation: "This scene is near the beginning of the movie; before Neo wakes up in the 'real world'. Trinity has been tasked with contacting Neo and bringing him to Morpheus; she finds him at a club; where he has gone out with a couple of friends. What Trinity is referring to; in the quote; is how Neo has suspicions of the existence of the Matrix.",
        options: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the training program that everyone misses the first time?',
        answer: 'The Jump Program',
        explanation: `"I'm trying to free your mind; Neo; but I can only show you the door. You're the one that has to walk through it. Tank; load the jump program. You have to let it all go; Neo; fear; doubt; and disbelief. Free your mind."`,
        options: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'During the opening sequence; who is the first person to speak?',
        answer: 'Cypher',
        explanation: `We do not see the speaker; but you hear Cypher's voice answer; "Yeah?" to which Trinity replies; "Is everything in place?"`,
        options: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'What scene opens "The Matrix"?',
        answer: 'Telephone conversation',
        explanation: "No; as far as we can tell; Agent Smith has only one tie! Seriously though; the telephone convesation is between Cypher & Trinity; and gives away much of the plot; although you wouldn't understand it at the time.",
        options: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'What was the first word that Cypher said; in the beginning sequence?',
        answer: '"Yeah?"',
        explanation: 'Shortly before Trinity says her first words; Cypher says "Yeah?" as soon as he picks up the phone.',
        options: ''
    },
    {
        question: "'Unfortunately no one can be told what the Matrix is; you have to see it for yourself.'",
        answer: 'Morpheus',
        explanation: 'Morpheus says this to Neo when he asks what the Matrix is. This is said during the progress to convince Neo that he is the One. Morpheus is played by Laurence Fishburne.',
        options: ''
    },
    {
        question: `Just prior to meeting with the Oracle; we see Morpheus' crew eating in the mess hall of the Nebuchadnezzer. According to Dozer the food they consume is 'a single-celled protein combined with synthetic aminos; vitamins
      and minerals.' According to Mouse; this food reminds him of which breakfast treat?`,
        answer: 'Tastee wheat',
        explanation: "The crew is rather cruel to Neo during this scene; Mouse claiming that the goop they eat is like 'runny eggs' and Apoc suggesting it has the consistency of 'a bowl of snot'. Mouse also suggests that it reminds him of 'Tastee Wheat'. Switch points out that Mouse has technically never tried Tastee Wheat; which elicits further philosophic discussion from Mouse. I sure hope that I; technically or otherwise; never have to try Tastee Wheat after having seen this film...",
        options: '[ Cream-o-wheat ] [ Tastee wheat ] [ Wheaties ] [ Wheat germ ]'
    },
    {
        question: "Neo's shocking extraction from the Matrix is the early climax of the film; but it also marks a new beginning. Before any explanations can be provided; however; Neo requires physical therapy to restore his atrophied muscles to health. During his therapy; Morpheus makes reference to which body part(s) that Neo has never used before?",
        answer: 'Eyes',
        explanation: `Along with electrically stimulating his atrophied muscles; Neo goes through surgery to have dozens of implants removed. During his rehabilitation; he complains that his eyes hurt; a result of never having used them
      before according to Morpheus. This line has double meaning. He literally has never used his eyes for their function; to see. He also has figuratively had his eyes opened to the real world.`,
        options: '[ Eyes ] [ Ears ] [ Mouth ] [ Brain ]'
    },
    {
        question: "'The Matrix' opens with a conversation; and a rather revealing one at that if one is paying attention. Which two characters have this introductory discussion?",
        answer: 'Trinity and Cypher',
        explanation: "This elucidating conversation includes a prediction by Cypher that 'we're gonna kill him'; in reference to Neo; and also initiates suspicion that an informant exists among the protagonists. Of course; a neophyte watcher of the film would not pick up these nuances; and the conversation comes off as mostly cryptic to the first-time viewer. Listening to the conversation again after having watched the film a number of times; however; allows for some keen insight.",
        options: '[ Trinity and Cypher ] [ Neo and Trinity ] [ Trinity and Morpheus ] [ Morpheus and Cypher ]'
    },
    {
        question: 'On what level do Neo and Trinity stop the elevator after the lobby shootout?',
        answer: '41',
        explanation: 'If you look when Trinity pushes the emergency stop button; it flashes "Level 41....Have a Nice Day".',
        options: ''
    },
]